{
	"translate": [
		{
			"question": "Comment dit-on '**please**' en fran√ßais ?",
			"answers": ["s'il vous pla√Æt", "sil vous plait", "s il vous plait"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Traduisez '**thank you**' en fran√ßais",
			"answers": ["merci"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Comment dit-on '**excuse me**' en fran√ßais ?",
			"answers": ["excusez-moi", "excusez moi", "excuse moi"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Traduisez '**I love you**' en fran√ßais",
			"answers": ["je t'aime", "je taime", "je t aime"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Comment dit-on '**good morning**' en fran√ßais ?",
			"answers": ["bonjour"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Traduisez '**good night**' en fran√ßais",
			"answers": ["bonne nuit"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Comment dit-on '**yes**' en fran√ßais ?",
			"answers": ["oui"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Traduisez '**no**' en fran√ßais",
			"answers": ["non"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Comment dit-on '**help**' en fran√ßais ?",
			"answers": ["aidez-moi", "aide moi"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Traduisez '**where is the bathroom**' en fran√ßais",
			"answers": ["o√π est la salle de bain", "ou est la salle de bain", "o√π sont les toilettes", "ou sont les toilettes"]
		},





		{
			"question": "Comment dit-on '**how are you**' en fran√ßais ?",
			"answers": ["comment √ßa va", "comment ca va", "ca va", "√ßa va"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Traduisez '**I'm sorry**' en fran√ßais",
			"answers": ["je suis d√©sol√©", "je suis desole", "desole", "d√©sol√©"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Comment dit-on '**see you later**' en fran√ßais ?",
			"answers": ["√† plus tard", "a plus tard", "plus tard"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Traduisez '**my name is**' en fran√ßais",
			"answers": ["je m'appelle", "je m appelle", "je mappelle", "mon nom est"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Comment dit-on '**good evening**' en fran√ßais ?",
			"answers": ["bonsoir"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Traduisez '**happy birthday**' üéâ en fran√ßais",
			"answers": ["joyeux anniversaire", "joyeux anniversaire"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Comment dit-on '**congratulations**' en fran√ßais ?",
			"answers": ["f√©licitations", "felicitations", "felicitation"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Traduisez '**do you speak English**' en fran√ßais",
			"answers": ["parlez-vous anglais", "parlez vous anglais"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Comment dit-on '**I don't understand**' en fran√ßais ?",
			"answers": ["je ne comprends pas", "je ne comprend pas"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Traduisez '**can you help me**' en fran√ßais",
			"answers": ["pouvez-vous m'aider", "pouvez vous m'aider", "pouvez vous m aider"]
		}
	],
	"choices": [
		{
			"question": "What is the capital of France?",
			"answers": ["Paris", "Madrid", "Barcelona", "Mexico"],
			"correct": 0
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of these is a famous French dish?",
			"answers": ["Croissant", "Ratatouille", "Bouillabaisse", "Pizza"],
			"correct": 1
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the official language of France?",
			"answers": ["German", "French", "Spanish", "Portuguese"],
			"correct": 1
		},
		{
			"question": "Which city is famous for the Eiffel Tower?",
			"answers": ["Marseille", "Nice", "Lyon", "Paris"],
			"correct": 3
		},
		{
			"question": "What currency is used in France?",
			"answers": ["Euro", "Dollar", "Pound", "Yen"],
			"correct": 0
		},
		{
			"question": "Which festival is famous for its carnival parades in France?",
			"answers": ["Nice Carnival", "Festival of Lights", "Avignon Festival", "Cannes Film Festival"],
			"correct": 0
		},
		{
			"question": "Which French artist is known for impressionist paintings?",
			"answers": ["Claude Monet", "Paul C√©zanne", "Edgar Degas", "Pierre-Auguste Renoir"],
			"correct": 0
		},
		{
			"question": "Which French region is famous for its wines?",
			"answers": ["Burgundy", "Alsace", "Bordeaux", "Champagne"],
			"correct": 2
		},
		{
			"question": "What river flows through Paris?",
			"answers": ["Rhine", "Seine", "Loire", "Garonne"],
			"correct": 1
		},
		{
			"question": "Which French writer wrote 'Les Mis√©rables'?",
			"answers": ["√âmile Zola", "Gustave Flaubert", "Marcel Proust", "Victor Hugo"],
			"correct": 3
		},
		

		{
			"question": "What is the largest museum in France?",
			"answers": ["Mus√©e d'Orsay", "Centre Pompidou", "Louvre Museum", "Rodin Museum"],
			"correct": 2
		},
		{
			"question": "Which French city is known for its annual film festival?",
			"answers": ["Cannes", "Lyon", "Marseille", "Bordeaux"],
			"correct": 0
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the name of the famous cathedral in Paris that was damaged by fire in 2019?",
			"answers": ["Notre-Dame", "Sainte-Chapelle", "Sacr√©-C≈ìur", "Saint-Sulpice"],
			"correct": 0
		},
		{
			"question": "Which French region is famous for producing Champagne?",
			"answers": ["Bordeaux", "Provence", "Burgundy", "Champagne"],
			"correct": 3
		},
		{
			"question": "Which French city is known as the 'City of Lights'?",
			"answers": ["Paris", "Nice", "Lille", "Strasbourg"],
			"correct": 0
		},
		{
			"question": "Which French king was known as the 'Sun King'?",
			"answers": ["Louis XIV", "Louis XVI", "Charles V", "Henry IV"],
			"correct": 0
		},
		{
			"question": "Which structure was gifted to the United States by France in 1886?",
			"answers": ["The Eiffel Tower", "The Statue of Liberty", "Arc de Triomphe", "Mont Saint-Michel"],
			"correct": 1
		},
		{
			"question": "Which French philosopher is known for the statement 'I think, therefore I am'?",
			"answers": ["Jean-Paul Sartre", "Ren√© Descartes", "Voltaire", "Michel Foucault"],
			"correct": 1
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the national motto of France?",
			"answers": ["Liberty, Equality, Fraternity", "Freedom, Justice, Peace", "Unity, Discipline, Work", "Truth, Honor, Valor"],
			"correct": 0
		},
		{
			"question": "Which mountain range forms the natural border between France and Spain?",
			"answers": ["Alps", "Pyrenees", "Appalachians", "Rockies"],
			"correct": 1
		}
	],
	
	"voices": [
		{
			"question": "Translate in english.",
			"file": "fr/i_love_bread.mp3",
			"answers": ["I like bread", "I love bread"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Translate in english.",
			"file": "fr/how_are_you.mp3",
			"answers": ["How are you ?", "How are you"]
		},

		{
			"question": "Translate in english.",
			"file": "fr/what_time.mp3",
			"answers": ["What time is it ?", "What time is it"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Translate in english.",
			"file": "fr/want_baguette.mp3",
			"answers": ["I want a baguette", "I want bread"]
		}
	]
}